<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="changelog">
        <item>
            3.2.5.2:\n
            - New Frog. Still doesn\'t spin.\n
            - Announcement parsing: Always be informed of new Kickparpers and other forum drama.\n
            - BBCode selection interface can now be used when creating private messages.\n
            - Slightly improved attachment handling.\n
            - Fixed giphy gif preview.\n
            - You can no longer disable hardware acceleration.\n
            - A few things you probably won\'t even notice.\n
            - A couple of crash fixes and lots and lots of backend stuff.
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.5.1:\n
            - Fully overhauled reply window. It\'s so new and shiny.\n
            - Fixed thread list without tags. Secondary tags (SAMART and A\/T) slightly offset in pre-Kitkat. WONTFIX, buy a new phone.\n
            - Fixed attachment downloads.\n
            - Fixed volume-button scrolling.\n
            - Fixed log-in during probations. Probably. Maybe. Did not test.
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.5.0c:\n
            - Fast fix for flickering frogs
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.5.0b:\n
            - Fix for crash when trying to view threads you have no permission to (e.g. accessing threads via bookmarks that are in the currently hidden GBS)
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.5.0:\n
            - Added \"Display Image\" options to the image action menus (the stuff that pops up when you tap on images). Zoom away!\n
            - Added basic PM notifications. \n
            - Rearranged image action menu in the process because I kept downloading images. Also replaced icon for \"Show inline image\"\n
            - If you have disabled gifs (as you should) tapping emoticons will now resume / pause their animation.\n
            - Enhanced the post preview so more things work. Should now mostly behave like the app except for videos and youtube. But you hopefully won\'t want to watch them in a post preview. Right?\n
            - Copied another thread tag from the iOS guys. If you see a thread tag that has not been remade yet you should visit their thread and tell them about it. If you post a proposal image, even better.\n
            - Prevent attaching images with unsupported resolution or filetype.\n
            - Attachments are now treated as images instead of links.\n
            - Fixed a few bugs that made you crash.\n
            - App is now water-resistant.
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.4.2:\n
            - Crash fix for pre-lollipop devices
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.4.1:\n
            - New design for forum index icon. Please tell us in one of the threads (preferably the beta one in the project.log forum) whether or not you like it\n
            - Post preview. Due to some very weird bug it only previews what the forums return, no stuff that needs javascript like webms and twitter embeds. Sorry.\n
            - Bugfixes
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.4.0:\n
            - New transition screen (that giant frog you just saw)\n
            - Reworked forum index, you can customise it in settings. Forums are now synced once a day\n
            - Added new thread tag (guess which one)\n
            - Ability to close and reopen threads\n
            - Fixed crash on Xiaomi devices (caused by them overriding one of our libraries with a version from 2008 :argh:)\n
            - Lots of work under the hood.
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.2:\n
            - Fixed bug in the PM view on pre-lollipop devices
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.1:\n
            - Fixed reporting\n
            - Fixed PM option on non-plat users\n
            - Added plat grenades\n
            - Added tags to PM view\n
            - Added more thread tags\n
            - Fixed space on the bottom of threads when using OLED theme
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.0c:\n
            - Now actually including the changes from 3.2.3.0b
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.0b:\n
            - Fixed a few crashes on older phones.\n
            - Fixed a bug where the app would crash at the end of the probation period. If it\'s still crashing you\'ll need to clear the app data. Serves you right for posting badly tough :colbert:
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.0:\n
            - Now with less action menu crashes.\n
            - HTTPS link handling
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.3:\n
            - This changelog.\n
            - New action menu for the post menu (Those three dots. No the other ones, the ones on every post). Much more customizable, no more reporting your own posts or marking yourself. Fix that removes the option to send PMs to non-plat users coming soon.\n
            - Some backend fixes
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.2:\n
            - Made some changes to combat the webm performance issues brought by the webview update: No information is preloaded so they might take a bit longer to start. Imgur webms have a thumbnail to alleviate that. Quoted webms no longer autoplay.\n
            - Updated some libraries for a tiny bit more performance\n
            - Fixed search results taking up an entire screen
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.1\n
            - Fix for empty threadview when returning to the app\n
            - Fix for threadview not responding when viewing thread with many webms\n
            - Dark theme split into dark and Oled\n
            - Theming changes here and there
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.0\n
            - added Search for plat users ( beta! - I mean OLD!)\n
            - Load forums via SSL\n
            - Webm/Gifv Videos out of view are paused, option to not autostart embedded videos in post settings. They\'ll stay unloaded and won\'t display a thumbnail cause Google hates you.\n
            - Made unloaded GIFs prettier for some hosts\n
            - Fixed FYAD GIF avatars\n
            - fixed and improved marking users (including fixing a crash when importing settings with marked users)\n
            - more thread tags
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>