<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="changelog">
        <item>
            3.2.4.0:\n
            - New transition screen (that giant frog you just saw)\n
            - Reworked forum index, you can customise it in settings. Forums are now synced once a day\n
            - Added new thread tag (guess which one)\n
            - Ability to close and reopen threads\n
            - Fixed crash on Xiaomi devices (cause by them overriding one of our libraries with a version from 2008 :argh:)\n
            - Lots of work under the hood.
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.2:\n
            - Fixed bug in the PM view on pre-lollipop devices
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.1:\n
            - Fixed reporting\n
            - Fixed PM option on non-plat users\n
            - Added plat grenades\n
            - Added tags to PM view\n
            - Added more thread tags\n
            - Fixed space on the bottom of threads when using OLED theme
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.0c:\n
            - Now actually including the changes from 3.2.3.0b
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.0b:\n
            - Fixed a few crashes on older phones.\n
            - Fixed a bug where the app would crash at the end of the probation period. If it\'s still crashing you\'ll need to clear the app data. Serves you right for posting badly tough :colbert:
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.3.0:\n
            - Now with less action menu crashes.\n
            - HTTPS link handling
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.3:\n
            - This changelog.\n
            - New action menu for the post menu (Those three dots. No the other ones, the ones on every post). Much more customizable, no more reporting your own posts or marking yourself. Fix that removes the option to send PMs to non-plat users coming soon.\n
            - Some backend fixes
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.2:\n
            - Made some changes to combat the webm performance issues brought by the webview update: No information is preloaded so they might take a bit longer to start. Imgur webms have a thumbnail to alleviate that. Quoted webms no longer autoplay.\n
            - Updated some libraries for a tiny bit more performance\n
            - Fixed search results taking up an entire screen
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.1\n
            - Fix for empty threadview when returning to the app\n
            - Fix for threadview not responding when viewing thread with many webms\n
            - Dark theme split into dark and Oled\n
            - Theming changes here and there
        </item>
        <item>
            3.2.2.0\n
            - added Search for plat users ( beta! - I mean OLD!)\n
            - Load forums via SSL\n
            - Webm/Gifv Videos out of view are paused, option to not autostart embedded videos in post settings. They\'ll stay unloaded and won\'t display a thumbnail cause Google hates you.\n
            - Made unloaded GIFs prettier for some hosts\n
            - Fixed FYAD GIF avatars\n
            - fixed and improved marking users (including fixing a crash when importing settings with marked users)\n
            - more thread tags
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>